days times would be two years that's 720
days and half a time would be half a
year that's 180 days making a total of
1,60 days but we know that in Bible
prophecy a day equals a year so it's
years all right so here's what happened
when Rome began to persecute the
Christians it failed Rome eventually
fell
and in 3113 a man by the name of
Constantine anyone ever heard of
Constantine
Constantine emperor of Rome became a
Christian and the church that had been
being persecuted
before decided to put their trust in an
emperor over their high
priest Jesus Christ in
heaven okay do you getar what I just
said does that sound familiar to you
do you remember what happened in the Old
Testament Israel decided that they
wanted a king's protection instead of
the priests as a result Constantine
began to mingle paganism with
Christianity anyone know this history
okay just sometime shorter a man by the
name of
Clovis who was the first king of the
Franks also converts to Christianity and
he gives his sword to assist the church
in persecuting those who did not believe
like them isn't that interesting the
devil works best on an with an
inside
job so notice what begins to happen in
other words what you begin H what you
have happening now is this mingling of
church and state where the state is now
dictating what the church does and as a
result this would eventually lead the
the the the the priests of the church to
reject the sanctuary just like Israel
had done in the Old
Testament watch watch this is absolutely
amazing guys list listen carefully in
the Old Testament Israel is set free by
the sacrifice of a Passover Lamb they
are given the literal Sanctuary but they
begin to put their trust in a King
instead of the priest the king usurps
the authority of the priesthood leads to
a defiling of the sanctuary by the
priesthood
Hof
Hood sets the way for them to reject the
first coming of Christ it was an inside
job an incredible parallel in the New
Testament spiritual Israel is set free
by the sacrifice of Christ they are
given the spiritual Sanctuary but they
begin to trust in an emper Emperor
instead of their high priest Jesus
Christ Emperor and state usurp the
authority of the church which will lead
to a defiling of the sanctuary Led Out
by the priests which prepares the way
from many to be unprepared for the
second coming of Christ and it is an
inside
job are you ready to see the inside job
are you sure you're ready
before we begin I need you to repeat
these words after
me
we
love
you
Pastor
Meyers
good
so the sacrifice of Christ which was to
be
sufficient for all sins for all times in
which Christ need only die once and that
sacrifice being made so that we can have
forgiveness of sins was altered and
changed after the rise of this power a
teaching was introduced called
indulgences in
which you have to pay to be forgiven for
sins now the sanctuary clearly points
out that Christ sacrifice would be
sufficient for the Forgiveness of sins
but now the people were being told
listen Christ sacrifice is really not
enough if you want to be forgiven you
have
to you've got to
pay now I want to ask you something
we're talking I want you to imagine now
we're living in a time of the Dark Ages
and you're poor peasant and you're being
told that in order for God to forgive
you you have to pay how would you begin
to feel about
God would you begin to have some Reserve
about this God being a god of
love this is what I
say I believe that Christ's death on the
cross is sufficient for the payment of
my how many of you agree with
that beloved listen listen carefully now
some of you in here may have been
brought up may have been dearly enamored
with that you know you understand what
I'm saying and you this may have been
all you've known but but the Bible is
telling you now that that you do not
have to pay anything for the Forgiveness
of your sins because Christ has done it
already
nothing it is a free gift all you need
to do is ask for it and once you ask for
it you don't need to come behind that
and say by the way let me give you
something some money just to
secure my
forgiveness that is not the character of
the god of Heaven the sanctuary points
that
out but there was
more because you see since
God destroyed anyone and everyone who
did not pay
indulgences and since God was a kind of
God that
would send babies to an eternally
burning
hell the teaching was
introduced that infants needed to be
sprinkled in order to be
saved
infant
sprinkling now I want you to imagine you
know you're living in that time and
you're being told that God is going to
send your baby that is about 3 days old
to hell if you do not sprinkle it the
baby has done no good and no
evil but God will put that baby in hell
so you've got a sprinkle it you can't
dip it on the water so best way to do it
is sprinkle it you see the Bible says
that we are to be the Bible says
repent and be
baptized can a two-year-old repent can a
two Monon old
repent so what it does is it takes away
the significance of what it truly means
to be converted and so this introduction
of sprink of infant sprinkling was
another attack upon the character of God
because it basically taught the people
that God destroys irregardless of your
ability to repent or not repent if
you're two-month old and you die too bad
that baby's going in hell but there is
hope if the price is
right you can get that baby out of
hell do do you see what's going on here
but it was an inside job and when you do
things on the inside on in the name of
God it may seem questionable but hey I
trust these guys they're the ones with
the Bible they're the ones that know
this stuff and I don't really know that
much so I trust them I'm going to put my
salvation in their hands because I think
that's what God would want me to do
anyway I believe
that to be baptized or to be re-baptized
is to be done by
immersion all the way under all the way
up you know what that signifies if if if
you've ever seen a
baptism a cloth is put over your nose it
means that you stop
breathing you go down in the water it
means you have been
buried you come back up out of the water
it means you you have been raised again
the cloth is
removed newness of
Life the spirit of God dwells in that
Tabernacle you become a living Temple
for
God but the only way it can happen is by
repentance you know what I I hear people
say all the time you know if you're a
Baptist I'm a fourth generation Baptist
you know you kind of proud about it I'm
4G
s right there is no such thing as a
fourth generation anything you're not
born something you must be born
again are you with me all right so let's
move
on uh next came the table of
showbread the word of God was cast down
and replaced with church
traditions in other words the teaching
came about that look the word of God is
yeah it's important but Traditions hold
a higher place with God than the word of
God and in fact the people were told you
can't even possess a Bible for yourself
only the priests can understand the word
of God and beloved basically what this
did was it it led the people to believe
look God doesn't really love me God is
not going to reveal his truth to me he's
only going to reveal it to the priest
and therefore I must put my trust in the
priest do you see what's going on here
the little horn is attacking the
sanctuary and in doing so he is
attacking the very character of God
according to Canon 14 the church Council
of too it says we prohibit also that Ley
should be permitted to have the books of
the old or new testament we most
strictly forbid their having any
translation of these books why in the
world would would would anyone who
claims to be f God want to put an edict
upon anyone else having the word of that
doesn't make sense to
me but this is what they were
taught I
believe that the word of God should be
followed over the traditions of men what
do you think how many of you agree with
that you know as we're going through
this beloved look if you haven't been
baptized if you were sprinkled you know
what I believe God is bringing you here
now for the opportunity to get it right
if you've been following tradition God
is bringing you here tonight giving you
the opportunity to get it right that's
what he's trying to do that's why you're
here
tonight God loves you he doesn't want to
see you lost or deceived or any or any
such thing what about number four the uh
Christ mediation as our high priest was
cast down and replaced by confessions to
the
priest in other words they were taught
that you don't go to God to ask for
forgiveness you have to come to the
priest and
confess now here's something very
interesting has anyone ever seen a
confessional
Booth it is a two compartment room
divided by a
curtain with a man sitting in the place
of hearing the confessions of other
men's sins
what did it teach the people God won't
listen to you he'll listen to the priest
but he won't listen to
you you see beloved I can imagine
growing up in that time and thinking man
whoever this God is he's not too
friendly whoever this God is I don't
like him too much hey but I don't want
to burn forever so we love you Lord and
we lift our hearts
[Laughter]
love through fear not good not
good the poor sinner kneels at his
confessor's feet he knows he is not
speaking to an ordinary man but to
another Christ
huh he hears the words I absolve thy
sins and the Hideous load of sins drops
from his soul forever that's in the book
shall I be a priest
I
believe that there is only one mediator
between God and man and that is the man
Jesus Christ anyone else in here believe
that if you haven't believed it before
now now is your opportunity to grab hold
beloved I know I know I know we think
man if I was back there when the Crisis
began in heaven I wouldn't have been
been one of those one-third of the
Angels but beloved here we are now and
some of us maybe many of us are in here
facing these realities now what am I
going to choose
it's live it's real
time how about this the light of the
church was cast down and replaced by
what I like to call the Dark Ages you
see the this power Cru uh uh persecuted
anyone that disagreed with their beliefs
that the Church of Rome has shed more
innocent blood than any other
institution that has ever existed among
mankind will be questioned by no
Protestant who has a competent his
knowledge of History it is impossible to
form a complete conception of this
multitude of her victims and it is quite
certain that no power of imagination can
adequately realize their sufferings
that's in the influence of the spirit of
rationalism in Europe Rome the Church of
Rome persecuted anyone that did not
believe like she believed and they
basically tried to shut down anyone
witnessing other than what she said and
I believe that God desires me us to let
our light shine by sharing with others
the truth truth that God reveals what do
you say about
that all
right number six the law of God was cast
down a change in God's law all right now
before we go further just want you to
repeat after me Pastor
Myers we still love
you as we had
said a little bit earlier all
right Daniel 7:25 says this he shall
think to what change times and laws I
want you to notice the pope this is a
Catholic
Source the pope has power to
change times to abrogate laws and to
dispense with all things even the
precepts of
Christ that's
strong that's strong and and this quote
parallel
Daniel
725 notice Isaiah 24 the Earth also is
defiled under the inhabitants thereof
because they have transgressed the law
changed the ordinance broken the
Everlasting Covenant therefore has the
curse devoured the Earth and they that
dwell therein are desolate therefore the
inhabitants of the Earth are burned and
few men left God pointed out ahead of
time that a power would rise that would
seek to change God's law and here we
have a direct statement saying the PO
hope is able and has power to change the
law of
God what law are you
ready the Bible says remember the
Sabbath remember that thou keep holy the
Sabbath day the Catholic Church says no
by my divine power I abolish the Sabbath
day and command you to keep the first
day of the week and lo the entire
civilized World bows down in reverent
obedience to the command of the Holy
Catholic
Church Catholic
Source the Bible says know ye not that
to whom you yield yourselves servants to
obey his servants you are to whom you
obey whether of sin unto death or of
obedience of obedience unto
righteousness can we play a little game
real quick uh Simon Says stand up
okay okay no no let's not do that Jesus
says stand up Jesus says stand
up and he does say stand up in the word
Jesus says stand
up all right maybe some of you can't
stand so you you're good you're good um
all
right Satan says sit
down okay Satan says stand up
Satan says stand up some of you are
still
standing all right okay very good very
good now you're probably wondering what
in the world have to do with anything
listen is there any sin in standing up
or sitting down is there anything wrong
in in the act of standing up or sitting
down no but who you live listen
to are you with who you obey makes what
all the difference in the world are you
with me so so for example God said don't
eat from this tree was there any sin in
the act of eating from a tree no but it
was who you listen to God said eat I
mean God said don't eat Satan said eat
and who you listen to makes all the
difference in the world are you with me
so if the Bible says remember the
seventh day to keep it holy the Sabbath
the seventh day of the week which
happens to be on
Saturday wait wait a
minute
what when my friend introduced me to
this and I I'm going to share this with
you can I share this with you real quick
um I was with a friend that I didn't
know you know didn't know any of this
and one day we were we were talking in
my house and he said uh hey um what day
is the Sabbath and I was like oh Sunday
everybody knows that and you know I was
with a couple other friends I started
high-fiving them then he was like um
what's the first day of the week and I
was like Sunday and then he was like
what's the seventh day of the week and I
was
like
Sunday wait a
minute and he actually took me to a
calendar and it was like I felt like you
know um can I say this word is
that okay I felt moronic I was like wait
a minute I'm looking at a calendar and
it's obvious that Sunday is the first
day of the week how come I did not know
this I mean it literally blew my mind
why because everyone I knew was going to
church on
Sunday and then when I looked at the
Commandment I was like wait a minute
well how did this happened and then he
began to share with me from the word of
God what I'm sharing with you now
beloved let me tell you something when
he was sharing this stuff with me I felt
I don't know if you ever had the feeling
like you were in a movie I felt like I
was in a movie discovering something
that was going to have a dramatic effect
on planet Earth like I don't it just
felt I was like well who else knows
this you know I in my mind I was like
all right I'm about to be the missionary
to the entire planet
yeah that's what I was thinking I didn't
know that there were other people that
believed it I had no clue I was just
like oh the Lord has qu okay about but
you understand it was like that like
like wow the world has to know
this the Catholic church for over 1,000
years before the existance of a
Protestant by virtue of her Divine
Mission did what change the day from
Sabbath from Saturday to Sunday that is
the Catholic mirror Catholic Universal
bulletin August 14 1942 the church
changed the observance of the Sabbath to
Sunday by right of the Divine infall
infallible Authority given to her by her
founder Jesus Christ inside
job you see beloved if the church says
hey we did it because God gave us
Authority then that sounds
good who would want to think anything
else and how dare you say something
anything bad about the
church think back to Lucifer's rebellion
in heaven why onethird of the Angels
were offended at God and said God we
don't want any more of
you think
back the Protestant anyone know what a
Protestant is it is one who claims to
follow the Bible and the Bible only the
Protestant claiming the Bible to be the
only god of faith has no warrant for
observing
Sunday you see Beloved the Catholic
Church says we believe in the Bible and
tradition and Sunday is not in the Bible
it's tradition but that's okay for us
because we believe tradition is more
authoritative than the word of God but
you Protestants who claim to follow the
Bible and the Bible only in keeping
Sunday you are actually giving reverence
to us why don't you just come back home
the protest is
over notice
this Catholic Source the pope and God
are the
same so he has all power in Heaven and
Earth how about this the pope this is
quoted in the York Catholic catechism
the pope takes the place of Jesus Christ
Christ on Earth by Divine Right the pope
has Supreme and full power in faith and
morals over each and every pastor of his
flock he is the true viker the head of
the entire church the father and teacher
of all Christians he is the infallible
ruler the founder of dogmas the author
of and the judge of councils the
universal ruler of Truth The Arbiter of
the world the Supreme judge of Heaven
and Earth the judge of all being judged
by no one God himself on Earth
beloved I'm not making this stuff up do
you understand what I'm saying and I
have no anger in my heart you know what
I believe that there are thousands and
millions of sincere Christians within
the Catholic church that love God with
all their heart I believe it I believe
it so please don't get me wrong or
mistaken okay but but but it's one thing
to love God it's another thing when a
system has a has a power pattern that is
not after the order of God God said the
Bible says thy way oh God is in a
sanctuary and this system says no we're
going to come in and kick the furniture
over and say no this is the way walking
in it do you see why it is so important
to understand the pattern that is
revealed to us in a sanctuary many of
you been coming been wondering okay
where is this going the sanctuary the
pattern okay I get the pattern but why
is it so important because beloved
without this it is impossible to
understand what the Book of Daniel The
Book of Revelation is trying to warn us
about when we have the GPS we can look
and say wait a minute this is not
according to the
GPS viker of Christ I want you to notice
the title viker of Christ the title of
the Pope implying his Supreme and
Universal Primacy both over both of
honor and of jurisdiction over the
Church of Christ that's according to the
new advent Catholic encyclopedia do you
know that the word viker means
substitute
in the place of the Greek form of the
word viker is
anti so the viker of Christ his title
viker of Christ means in the place of
Christ the Greek version is
anti christ
the letters inscribed on the Pope's
miter are these vicarius fil which is
Latin for the viker of the Son of God
that's from our Sunday visitor Catholic
weekly V weekly uh April 18th 1915 so
the pope has a crown uh of uh in his
miter and these are the letters that
were once inscribed there vicarius fil
if you take those letters which are
Latin letters that's a Latin word and
you apply the Roman numerical value for
each letter V being five I is 1 C is 100
a r i is 1 U is 5 S is zero that equals
one2 fi equals 53 d d being 500 I being
1 is 501 you add them together and you
come up with a number
666 it's an inside job
guys it's an inside
job John White I don't know if any of
you knew this but I'm going to read a
couple quotes to you please listen
carefully John Whitecliff said this when
the western church was divided about 40
years between the two rival popes one in
Rome and the other the other in aagon
France each pope called the other Pope
Antichrist and John Whitecliff is
reputed to have regarded them as both
being
right two Hal of antichrist make up the
perfect man of sin between
them that's John whitecliffe the f
Martin Luther do we have any Lutheran
you know any you haven't found him as a
Lutheran how many of you are familiar
with the Lutheran Church listen to what
Martin Luther the founder of the
Lutheran Church said we here are of the
conviction that the papacy is the seat
of the true and real Antichrist
personally I declare that I owe the pope
no other obedience than that to
Antichrist this is the teaching of the
Lutheran Church by the way they don't
teach that anymore
and we're going to find out why how
about this one John Knox anyone ever
heard of John Knox founder of the
Presbyterian Church says this the
Tyranny which the pope himself has for
so many ages exercised over the church
and that the pope should be recognized
as the very Antichrist the son of
predition of whom Paul speaks it's not
the individual it's the title it's the
position that claims to sit in the place
of God that is Antichrist John Calvin
said this some persons think us too
severe and censorious when we call the
Roman pontiff Antichrist but those who
are of this opinion do not consider that
they bring the same charge of
presumption against Paul himself after
whom we speak and whose language we
adopt I shall briefly show that Paul's
words in 2 Thessalonians 2 are not
capable of any other interpretation than
that which applies them to the
papacy that is John John Calvin my
friends Roger Williams of the Baptist
Church spoke of the Pope as the
pretended viker of Christ on Earth who
sits as God over the temple of God
exalting himself not only above all that
is called God but over the souls and
consciences of all his vassels yay over
the spirit of Christ over the Holy
Spirit yay and God himself speaking
against the god of Heaven thinking to
change times and laws but he is the son
of predition
John Wesley any Methodist in the House
John Wesley of the Methodist movement
said this speaking of the Antichrist he
said he is an emphatical sense the man
of sin as he increases all manner of sin
above measure and he is to properly
style the son of predition as he has
caused the death of numberless
multitudes both of his opposers and
followers he it is that exalts himself
above all that is called God or that is
worshiped claiming the highest power and
the highest honor claiming the
prerogatives which belong to God Alone
beloved it is absolutely amazing I
believe that God desires me to keep his
Commandments as Jesus kept
them I desire to obey God this is my
personal desire guys I desire to obey
God and through his strength keeping the
Commandments including the seventh day
beloved listen to me that Mercy Seat God
wants to get us under it but if there's
a law that we reject in that underneath
that Mercy Seat we're moving ourselves
out from under the mercy seat all we
need to do is reject one
commandment do you know that cyanide is
most dangerous when it's placed in a
pure glass of water who in here would
drink a whole glass of
cyanide but put a drop of cyanide in the
water and it is more easy to
swallow on the Sabbath commandment not a
big deal it's just a day can you imagine
Eve it's just a
tree how about this according to 1
Corinthians 3:16 the Bible says know you
not that you're the temple of God and
the spirit of God dwells in you if any
man defy the temple of God him shall God
destroy for the temple of God is Holy
which Temple you are we read in Isaiah
66:17 they that sanctify themselves and
purify themselves in the gardens behind
one tree in the midst eating swine's
flesh and the Abomination and the mouth
shall be consumed together so God is
saying look don't eat the unclean thing
do you know that this little horn power
defile the sanctuary not only
spiritually but also literally listen
Constantine called a gathering of
Christian monkss with a view to the
formulation of obligatory religious
beliefs however some of them disagreed
with this text there was a cision in the
symbol of faith which had been formatted
was not regarded as valid thereupon 318
men gathered in NAA and formulated a
symbol of faith which was accepted and
made obligatory by Constantine people
who descended from it were killed and
professions of Faith differing from it
suppressed in this way people who
profess the religion of Christ came to
do all that is reprehensible they
worshiped the cross observed the Roman
religious rights and ate
poor wow those who did not eat it were
killed
you see Beloved the early Christian
Church understood that their temp their
bodies were the temple and they were to
keep it clean but then another system
comes in and says oh yeah God cleansed
All
Things Not only did they did that lead
to defiling spiritually but the defiling
literally of the temple how about
alcohol in the
temple that cup that cup do you know the
Bible describes it says here and the
woman was arrayed in purple and scarlet
color do you know that in Bible prophecy
a woman represents a
church the woman was a there's only one
church that is Aid in purple and Scarlet
and Deck with gold a rich Church
precious stones and Pearls having a
golden cup in her hand full of
Abominations and filthiness of her
fornication and upon her forehead was a
name written mystery Babylon the great
the mother of harlots and Abominations
of the earth and I saw the woman drunk
with the blood of the Saints this is an
exact description of the Church of the
Dark Ages literal Babylon cast down the
sanctuary defied the law of God forced
the people to un to eat unclean
Foods spiritual Babylon cast down the
Heavenly truths of the Heavenly Temple
defies the law of God and leads to the
defiling of the body Temple through diet
wow wow every article of furniture is
counterfeited by the
system see that crucifix
ward off evil spirits taking the Cross
of Christ and using it for a
superstitious
purpose ever been into a church where
you see
that holy water to cast off evil
spirits candles to ward off evil
spirits The Bread and Wine table of
showbread this is the body of Christ
every time we break it Christ dies again
no Christ only died once
confessional Booth altar of
incense I don't know if you noticed the
two covering
cherubs and he is called the
Holy
Father beloved if if one part of the Su
fit that would be one thing but to have
this these many things fitting one power
now you can understand why the reformers
said it can fit no other power but this
power we're not talking about
individuals we're talking about systems
are you with
me God has sincere individuals within
this system the Bible says the 70 Beeks
of Daniel are 490 days to the Messiah
were fulfilled as 490 years I'm sorry
not the Bible not the Bible excuse me
this is Dr Henry Gratton and he's
quoting he's talking about the the the
1260 year prophecy it says um
on this scale the 42 months or 1260 days
are 1260 years we ask then has the
papacy endure this period an examination
of The Facts of History will show that
it has this is not something unique this
is something that that was being taught
everywhere listen what is that
1260 year time period the Roman Church
power became Supreme in Christendom in
538 ad due to a letter of the Roman
Emperor for Justinian known as
Justinian's decree which set up and
acknowledged the bishop of Rome as the
head of all churches listen very
carefully the church began to dominate
in 538 ad when the pope became the new
emperor of Rome are you with me church
and state officially under a pope no
longer an emperor but under a pope
exactly
1260 years later in
1798 birth year of France made his
entrance into Rome and abolished the
papal government and established a
secular
one think about this the Bible in the
time of Daniel says this little horn
will dominate for
1260 years in
538 this power is set up by the way who
remembers what kingdom it was that
helped the little horn get set up
the
Franks which is known as France check
this out guys the same power that set
the church on its path to political and
religious dominance is the same
power
1260 years later that took it out of
power how mindblowing is that
this is known as the
French
Revolution
now can you give me a little more time
guys are you
good please I'm I'm I'm I'm at my last
section here and then we'll we'll be
finished with this but please I thank
you for being so merciful and patient
with me as I am just excited up here all
by
myself I just thank
you all right so so listen
listen uh according to Blackwood
magazine this is November 1870 France is
the only nation in the world concerning
that which the authentic record survives
that as a nation she lifted her hand in
open Rebellion against the author of the
universe plenty of blasphemers plenty of
infidels there have been and still
continue to be in England Germany Spain
and elsewhere but France stands apart in
the world's history as the single state
by which the decree of her legislative
assembly pronounced said there was no
God and of which the entire population
of the capital and a vast majority
elsewhere women as well as men danced
and sang with joy in acceptance of the
announcements this is talking about the
French Revolution uh there's a reason
why I'm bringing this up okay um it was
not until the late 18th century during
the French Revolution that atheism
atheism what everyone atheism quite
literally exploded on the world scene
listen there were atheists before and
always have been but but atheism really
got its thrust in the French Revolution
which happened to take place at the end
of the
1260 years what is
atheism it is a rejection of God listen
carefully guys we're we're wrapping this
up listen
carefully almost out of nowhere as if it
had been Loos from an abyss atheism Rose
upon the world seeing ready to Devour
the religious powers that had so
ruthlessly dominated societ
before it did did you catch that
listen the world for the first time
heard an assembly of men born and
educated in civil civilization and
assuming the right to govern one of the
finest of the European nations lift up
their United voice to deny the most
solemn truth which man's Soul receive
and renounce unanimously the belief and
worship of a deity in other words they
actually made a law that there was no
God
some interesting points about the French
Revolution Christianity was abolished
for 3 and a half
years a 10day week was introduced to
remove the creation
account people celebrated in the streets
how many of you ever heard of a
scientist by the name of JB
Lamar JB Lamar was the Forerunner of
Darwin he is the first scientist to
promote to to uh introduce the the
concept of
evolution it was a denial of the
creation account in Genesis saying no no
no not that Evolution and it came out of
the
French
Revolution anyone ever heard of the
terms left and right in politics do you
know that they have their origin in the
French
Revolution the left represented the
liberal you know against God the right
represented those who were for the king
and for the church and in the French
Revolution the left ended up like wiping
out the
right persecution happened it was called
the reign of terror blood ran in the
streets it was a it was an incredible in
instable time and it was all because
check this out today's
liberalism rose out of the French
Revolution this is very important to
understand guys listen a a secular
scientist British secularist and joural
editor GW foot wrote this in
1915 who was the cause of the terror
talking about the French Revolution the
Christian monarchies that declared war
on free thinking fre free thinkers and
regicides theirs was the guilt and they
are responsible for the
Bloodshed let me explain to you what's
going on
here because of all that the church had
done during the Dark Ages in twisting
the truths of God and making God God
look like a
tyrant atheism was the natural
response do you guys catch this if this
is who God is I want nothing to do with
him Adam Clark said this in prophetic
language a Time signifies a year Adam
Clark by the way is a Methodist scholar
uh it says a prophetic year has a year
for each day three years and a half a
day standing for a year will amount to
1,260 years if we knew precisely when
the papal power began to exert its a
itself in an antichrist way then we
could at once fix the time of its
destruction the end is probably not very
distant it has already been grievously
shaken by the French in 1798 the French
Republican Army under General birth of
year took possession of the city of Rome
and the entire and entirely superseded
the whole papal
power this is not a unique
interpretation David Samson says this uh
uh it is not is it not remarkable and
powerfully confir conf a powerful
confirmation of the truth of scriptures
Prophecy of the scripture prophecy that
1260 years ago from the present 17 he
was writing this in
1798 in the very year the beginning of
538 Bel bellarus put an end to the
Empire at of the Goths at Rome leaving
no power therein but the bishop of the
Metro of the Metropolis read these
things in the uh in the prophetic
scriptures and compare them cooly with
the present state of Europe and then I
say again deny the truth of divine
revelation if you can open your eyes and
behold these things are these things
accomplished uh in the face of the whole
world this is not done in a corner he
wrote this in
1798 when Christianity was a dominant
religious political power during the AR
ages atheism was obscure atheists were
openly persecuted but it was not until
the French Revolution listen I'm G put
my slide down I'm going to finish the
rest of this without my slides
okay listen
carefully in Revelation 11 the Bible
describes it let me just read it there
was given me a read like unto a rod and
the angel stood saying rise and measure
the temple of God and the Altar and them
that worship therein but the court which
is without the temple leave out and
measure it for it is given unto the
Gentiles and the holy city shall they
tread Under Foot 40 and2 months and I
will give power unto my two witnesses
and they shall prophesy
1,23 score days clothed in sackcloth I'm
sorry I'm going to go to my
slide and when they shall have finished
their testimony the Beast that ascends
out of the bottomless pit shall make war
against them and shall overcome them and
kill them and their dead bodies shall
lie in the street of the great city
which is spiritually called Sodom in
Egypt where also our Lord was crucified
and they of the people and kindreds and
tongues and Nations shall see their dead
bodies three days and a half how much is
three days and a half three and a half
what years someone was dead for three
and a half years in the streets of this
place and they shall rejoice they that
dwell upon the Earth shall rejoice over
them and make Merry and shall send gifts
one to another because these two
prophets had tormented them I want you
to notice this the two witnesses
prophesy for how long 1260 days listen
carefully how much is 1260 days really
1260 years so what we're talking about
is the very same time period of the 1260
years so what would be the two witnesses
that prophesy it's very
simple no one lives 12 1,260 years
so it's symbolic of something Jesus said
search the scriptures for they testify
of me do you know that the the Bible is
made up of the Old Testament and the New
Testament they are
witnesses so these two witnesses
prophesied under hiding why because the
church didn't allow anyone to have
Bibles that's how they did their work
for the 1260 years but at the end of
this time the Bible says this Beast
would arise now what does a beast
represent in the Bible a Kingdom or
Nation so we're looking for a nation
that would Arise at the end of the 1260
years that would war against the Bible
and celebrate that the Bible had been
wiped out what nation are we talking
about we're talking about France check
this out the Bible prophesied the rise
of atheism
just GNA wait
here The Atheist who says there is no
God this massive movement today of
atheism we can be good without God that
they claim yes we originated we really
got our push from the French Revolution
the Bible says oh by the way um just so
that you know I am God I prophesy that
this would happened in the very time
that it
happened what
all right so what does all this mean
look let's just move through going to my
last slide here by the way all of this
humanism relativism sexual Liberty uh
National atheism all of it rose out of
the French Revolution
now my
point does this look familiar to you I
stood upon the sand of the sea and saw a
beast rise about the sea this is this is
uh John the Revelator speaking and he
says I saw a beast rise about the sea
what does a beast represent a kingdom
having seven heads and 10 horns does
that sound familiar everyone same Beast
that Daniel saw all right but now he's
seeing it as one and it has the names of
Blas for me the Beast which I saw was
like unto a leopard familiar feet of a
bear yes mouth of a lion uh-huh all this
is new is is the same thing the dragon
gave him his power his seed is great
Authority and notice this I saw one of
his heads as it were wounded to death
and his deadly wound was healed and all
the world wondered after the
Beast okay now I can leave my slides
Jackie please come
come this Beast is set to receive a
deadly wound but that the wound would be
what healed listen carefully guys the
Beast represents the papal system when
was it wounded 1798
but the Bible tells us that the wound
would be
healed I got a question for
you do you know that in the 1950s a pope
was not allowed on on American soil
because America was formed so that we
could leave the religious persecution of
Europe and so we said we'll never have a
pope and we'll never have a
king
today it's a totally different story
the deadly wound is
healing and the world is wondering
after the beast in fact they are saying
who is like unto the Beast who would
ever want to make war with
him can I share this with
you there is a reason why the world is
wondering after the Beast you may not
have noticed this but the Bible said
this Beast was coming up out of the
sea does anything else come to mind when
you think of someone coming up out of
water what do you think of baptism what
does baptism a symbol of
death burial
resurrection and you're now a new
man the Beast is coming up out of the
sea
[Music]
hey look the Dark Ages that was the old
us we've changed it's a new us now we've
been
baptized but there's a problem guys you
see listen the word of God is designed
to put us to death and then we're born
again but the Beast was only wounded
it did not die what I'm trying to tell
you beloved is that unless there is full
repentance for our sins you
cannot be born
again there is no change and today guess
what the church has not repented of
their change of the Sabbath they have
not repented of this teaching of
indulgences they have not repented of
the infant sprinkling and and and and uh
uh um you know uh baptizing without
confession and repentance they have
repented of these things and if there's
no repentance it means you are only
wounded by the sword oh that hurt many
of us have only been wounded By The
Sword the Bible says the word of God is
quick powerful sharper than any
two-edged
sword many of us hear the preaching of
the word of God oh that hurt but we were
only wounded we didn't allow the sword
to slay us
the old man so that we could have
newness of
Life beloved tonight I cannot close
without giving you the opportunity
ushers please bring those cards I cannot
close without giving you the opportunity
to say tonight I will not be like those
angels in heaven who rejected truth
because they were blinded by love or
Affinity to someone or
something please as you listen to the
song tonight I urgently plead with you I
plead with
you make that decision to follow God
fully to keep his Commandments fully I
believe the spirit of God is convicting
Souls tonight and God is simply asking
make that decision please as you listen
to the song will you decide to keep
God's Commandments as he wrote them with
his own hand will you decide to follow
Jesus no matter where
he takes
[Music]
you this is my
desire to
hon
you Lord with all my heart I worship you